<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Thirty Days Of Wellness</string>
    <string name="d1">Day 1</string>
    <string name="d2">Day 2</string>
    <string name="d3">Day 3</string>
    <string name="d4">Day 4</string>
    <string name="d5">Day 5</string>
    <string name="d6">Day 6</string>
    <string name="d7">Day 7</string>
    <string name="d8">Day 8</string>
    <string name="d9">Day 9</string>
    <string name="d10">Day 10</string>
    <string name="d11">Day 11</string>
    <string name="d12">Day 12</string>
    <string name="d13">Day 13</string>
    <string name="d14">Day 14</string>
    <string name="d15">Day 15</string>
    <string name="d16">Day 16</string>
    <string name="d17">Day 17</string>
    <string name="d18">Day 18</string>
    <string name="d19">Day 19</string>
    <string name="d20">Day 20</string>
    <string name="d21">Day 21</string>
    <string name="d22">Day 22</string>
    <string name="d23">Day 23</string>
    <string name="d24">Day 24</string>
    <string name="d25">Day 25</string>
    <string name="d26">Day 26</string>
    <string name="d27">Day 27</string>
    <string name="d28">Day 28</string>
    <string name="d29">Day 29</string>
    <string name="d30">Day 30</string>

    <string name="d1h">Spend 15 min Outdoors</string>
    <string name="d2h">Listen to a Podcast or Audiobook</string>
    <string name="d3h">Have Sufficient Sleep</string>
    <string name="d4h">Stay Hydrated</string>
    <string name="d5h">Rest for some time</string>
    <string name="d6h">Meditate</string>
    <string name="d7h">Do Yoga or Stretching</string>
    <string name="d8h">Walk</string>
    <string name="d9h">Run for a minute</string>
    <string name="d10h">Listen to music</string>
    <string name="d11h">Pet a dog</string>
    <string name="d12h">Say Thank You</string>
    <string name="d13h">Show Kindness</string>
    <string name="d14h">Pray to God</string>
    <string name="d15h">Learn to say NO</string>
    <string name="d16h">Be Punctual</string>
    <string name="d17h">Smile</string>
    <string name="d18h">Workout</string>
    <string name="d19h">Disconnect</string>
    <string name="d20h">Get Fresh Air</string>
    <string name="d21h">Read</string>
    <string name="d22h">Write</string>
    <string name="d23h">Be Creative</string>
    <string name="d24h">Talk to someone</string>
    <string name="d25h">Have a Tea or a Coffee</string>
    <string name="d26h">Laugh</string>
    <string name="d27h">Eat Healthy</string>
    <string name="d28h">Be Optimistic</string>
    <string name="d29h">Try Something New</string>
    <string name="d30h">Invest in Personal Hygiene</string>

    <string name="d1t">Put some time on your calendar to take a walk outside or maybe even take a meeting while you\'re strolling through your neighbourhood.</string>
    <string name="d2t">Listen to a podcast and explore on a topic you have been itching to learn more about or discover a completely new topic that excites you.</string>
    <string name="d3t">I know why many people struggle with this one – not enough hours in the day, right? I\'m here to tell you that, however you need to re-prioritize your time to get those 7ish hours, figure it out. It\'s a big deal.</string>
    <string name="d4t">There are no downsides to drinking lots of water – and it\'s free and easy, so there\'s no reason not to do it.</string>
    <string name="d5t">With so many actions to take and things to do, remember that not doing something is one of the best ways to wellness. Whether planning to take a rest day from working out or simply taking time to relax instead of clean the house, run the errand, cook the meal, etc., rest does wonders for the body and mind.</string>
    <string name="d6t">Meditation in the morning and at night is the best way to relieve stress, calm the mind and thus helps increase focus.</string>
    <string name="d7t">Yoga is an amazing way to start the day, a quick mid-day stretch helps re-energize and refocus the mind, and a little evening wind down could help with calming the mind and lead to better sleep. Any time of day, for at least a minute, give the body a good stretch.</string>
    <string name="d8t">Similar to drinking lots of water, there are few downsides to walking – and it\'s free and easy, so there\'s no reason not to do it (unless physical issues prevent it).</string>
    <string name="d9t">Just one minute. That\'s all. And if it feels good, do it for one more minute… and maybe another.</string>
    <string name="d10t">Whether hard rock, folk, pop, or country, virtually any type of music can have uplifting benefits, motivate through a tough workout, or boost productivity with mundane tasks.</string>
    <string name="d11t">I get it, not everyone loves dogs. Actually, I don\'t get it. Dogs are the best. Petting dogs is a wonderful, happy act.</string>
    <string name="d12t">More than just in a way to show gratitude, thank you can be better swapped for one overused phrase. We have a tendency to say, \"I\'m sorry,\" too much; often for things we have no reason to be sorry. Instead of the default response, try instead thanking someone. Instead of, \"I\'m sorry I was late,\" try, \"Thank you for being patient.\"</string>
    <string name="d13t">Whether to someone else or yourself, kindness brings wellness. Again, be the source of positivity and uplifting to others, not negativity and bringing down others.</string>
    <string name="d14t">Prayer gives you a connection to something greater than yourself, which does wonders for your emotional well-being. It provides a greater sense of purpose, betters your mood, and helps you cope with and overcome the difficulties life brings your way.</string>
    <string name="d15t">Setting boundaries and better prioritize time by saying \"no\" occasionally is healthy. I\'m going put this out there for drugs, alcohol, and smoking. None of them are good for you and they affect the health and wellness of those around you, too. So just say no.</string>
    <string name="d16t">Being late leads to anxiety and stress – unless you\'re one of those people who runs on their own schedule and doesn\'t give AF about others\' time. So, assuming you do care, take time to plan ahead better, allow more time, and be intentional so you\'re on time rather than frantically running late.</string>
    <string name="d17t">Would you believe there are health benefits to smiling? It\'s true, from releasing endorphins to lowering blood pressure, the simple act of smiling more is an easy way to be well.</string>
    <string name="d18t">Physical fitness is as much necessary as mental, moreover your mental health greatly depends on your physical health. So start exercising once in a day.</string>
    <string name="d19t">Netflix, social media, notifications, emails – all necessary in our modern world but also can be huge, pointless time sucks that, late at night, stimulate the brain and interfere with sleep.</string>
    <string name="d20t">Unless it\'s frigidly cold, windy, or the snow drifts are blocking your door, make time to get outside for fresh air every day.</string>
    <string name="d21t">And I\'m not talking social media. I\'m talking something real and tangible with a positive message, one that expands your thinking, or one that teaches you something of value.</string>
    <string name="d22t">There\'s something about writing every day that I believe is good for the mind and soul. Whether a simple, daily note or full journaling effort, try writing for better wellness.There\'s something about writing every day that I believe is good for the mind and soul. Whether a simple, daily note or full journaling effort, try writing for better wellness.</string>
    <string name="d23t">Think out of the box on your subject, expand your mind and try to not be afraid of failure while doing that.</string>
    <string name="d24t">Texting, emails, DMs – none of them replace good old face-to-face conversation. Talking with a friend or family member and having connection brings big benefits.</string>
    <string name="d25t">A little caffeine is good – plus, if you get it with a friend, you get the added health of connection.</string>
    <string name="d26t">The saying, \"Laughter is the best medicine,\" exists for a reason. Both short-term and long-term benefits come from laughing.</string>
    <string name="d27t">A healthy diet is essential for good health and nutrition. It protects you against many chronic noncommunicable diseases, such as heart disease and diabetes.</string>
    <string name="d28t">Having a positive attitude opens your mind to trying new methods, adapting to new technologies, and identifying opportunities.</string>
    <string name="d29t">Going outside the comfort zone is how we grow, experience new thrills, and do great things. Sometimes, going out on a limb might bring failure – and, remember, it\'s okay to fail. Just learn from it.</string>
    <string name="d30t">Proper personal hygiene supports a strong immune system, which serves as the body\'s natural defence against infections.</string>
    <string name="expand_button_content_description">See what to do on this day.</string>

</resources>